Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005; 219087
  - Inside NYU: Archives, Stand-ups, and more, 22 Jul 2005; cuid1339; 243069; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Marvin Taylor and the Fales Library, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1340; 243070; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Conjunctions 25th Anniversary Reading, 7 Dec 2006; cuid1341; 243071; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Tony Judt Lecture: "Disturbing the Peace", 4 Dec 2006; cuid1342; 243072; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Fales Food Series: "What's with all these books on food?", 12 Dec 2006; cuid1343; 243073; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Translating the World: Engaging Americans in International Journalism, 2 Feb 2007; cuid1344; 243074; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - MLK Celebration Week at NYU: A Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, 17 Jan 2007; cuid1345; 243075; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Moving Archipelago: A Century of Writing Filipino America, 11 Nov 2007; cuid1346; 243076; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Entering at One's Own Rish: Dennis Cooper and Transgressive Writing, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1347; 243077; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - US Senator Charles E. Schumer (D-NY) at NYU, 21 Feb 2007; cuid1348; 243078; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Sharing the Life of Lisa Ellen Goldberg Memorial, 25 Feb 2007; cuid1349; 243079; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1350; 243080; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1351; 243091; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 76)
  - Artist's Circles: How do they work and what do they do?, 25 Jan 2007; cuid1352; 243081; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU's Media Talk: The Literary Life and the Print Editor's changing role in the world of Web 2.0 with Mr. Carr, 20 Mar 2007; cuid1353; 243092; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Moving Beyond Rhetoric and Toward Solutions, 30 Jan 2007; cuid1354; 243095; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Public Health, 27 Feb 2007; cuid1355; 243096; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Library: Harry Frankfurt, 19 Mar 2007; cuid1356; 243097; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1357; 243098; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1358; 243099; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 76)
  - Courant Masters Orientation, 11 Jan 2007; cuid1359; 243100; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Fales lecture B-Roll "Up is Up, But so is Down", 26 Oct 2007; cuid1360; 243101; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Fales: Writing New York Talks from Gotham City, 17 Apr 2007; cuid1361; 243102; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Leonard N. Stern Schoiol of Business: Ashok Sani, 27 Mar 2007; cuid1362; 243103; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - After CBGB: Gender, Sexuality, and the Future of Subculture, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1363; 243104; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - MIAP & ITP: A Talk with Archivist & Visual Designer, 23 Mar 2007; cuid1364; 243105; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Cooking with Color, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1365; 243106; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Greg Albanis - Security Training for Commencement, 22 Mar 2007; cuid1366; 243107; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Gallatin Panel: Body Image, 29 Mar 2007; cuid1367; 243108; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Casa Italiana, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1368; 243121; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Downtown Gallery B-Roll, 6 Feb 2006; cuid1369; 243124; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Downtown Galley Grey Art Gallery Tour, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1370; 243128; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Downtown Show Art Clips for Grey Art Gallery, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1371; 243129; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1372; 243132; 6 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1373; 243135; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Politics & Parnoia Opening and Panels, 31 Mar 2007; cuid1374; 243141; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Building a Food Professional Pedigree: New Roads to Knowledge and Success, 14 Jun 2007; cuid1375; 243142; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr.Wanda, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1376; 243147; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Pedro Noguera, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1377; 243148; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Aretha Ball, 19 Jul 2007; cuid1378; 243150; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Stern: Credit Crunch and Subprime Markets, 5 Nov 2007; cuid1379; 243160; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - College of Arts and Science Fall 2007, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1380; 243161; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Israel at 60, 9 Dec 2007; cuid1381; 243164; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - A/P/A YellowFace Interview, 8 Dec 2007; cuid1382; 243165; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Thirteen/WNET "Can We Disagree", 1 Jan 2008; cuid1383; 243169; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Reynolds Social Entrepreneurship in the 21st Century, 30 Jan 2008; cuid1384; 243172; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - All Library Staff Meeting "Creating the 21st Century Library", 8 Jan 2008; cuid1385; 243175; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Presidential Representitives on Transportation Panel, 31 Jan 2008; cuid1387; 243193; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Hidgon Class, 7 Feb 2008; cuid1388; 243196; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Reality Show 2006, 25 Sept 2006; cuid1389; 243212; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYDIS Clergical Summit, 1 Jun 2007; cuid1390; 243214; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Town Hall Meeting, 16 Nov 2006; cuid1391; 243216; 3 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Shoot, 15 Sep 2006; cuid1392; 243218; 3 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Downtown Show at Grey Art Gallery, undated; cuid1393; 243221; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Philanthropy Interviews, Nov 2006; cuid1394; 243223; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - How to Strengthen Communities to Solve Tough Societal Problems, 24 Jan 2006; cuid1395; 243225; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - James Hanley and Susana Piscitiello, undated; cuid1396; 243226; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Mock Solicitation Audit, 5 Apr 2007; cuid1397; 243227; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1398; 243237; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1399; 243238; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - MIAP Fall 2005 Speaker Series: A Mexican, 14 Oct 2005; cuid1400; 243239; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting and Dinner Final Edit, 7 Jul 2003; cuid1401; 243240; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYU Show #2, undated; cuid1402; 243242; 1 videocassettes (digital betacam) (Box 77)
  - Conference on Our Design, 5 Jun 2004; cuid1403; 243246; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music: Year 1, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1404; 243247; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Thomas Bornemann, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1405; 243248; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - New York University Ultraviolet Live 2008, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1406; 243250; 10 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1407; 243253; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1408; 243257; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 77)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: An Evening with James Schamus, 12 Mar 2008; cuid1409; 243258; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Hidden Hunger, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1410; 243271; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - APA Food Series: Why are we Afraid of Food?, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1411; 243272; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Fales Food Series: The Power of the Pen, 13 Mar 2008; cuid1412; 243273; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYU's Media Talk Series, 25 Mar 2008; cuid1413; 243274; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Courant Oral History Project: Louis Nirenberg, 23 Feb 2007; cuid1414; 243275; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Human Resources, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1415; 243276; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Stern CFR Panel, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1416; 243289; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Fales Library: Dennis Cooper Reading and Panel, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1417; 243290; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - 2007 Albert Gallatin Lecture "Defending Rights Without Courts and Judges", 10 Dec 2007; cuid1418; 243291; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - The Invisible Cure: Africa, the West, and the Fight against AIDS", 4 Dec 2007; cuid1419; 243292; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Library Staff Meeting, 1 Jan 2008; cuid1420; 243293; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Central HR I-9 Training, 8 Jan 2008; cuid1421; 243294; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - MLK Celebration Week: Marquee Event, 24 Jan 2008; cuid1422; 243295; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - New York Institute of Philosophy: Ronald Dworkin, 13 Nov 2007; cuid1423; 243296; 3 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1424; 243297; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1425; 243298; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1426; 243299; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Jonathan Lear, 17 Nov 2008; cuid1427; 243300; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - NYU Wagner Reynolds Speaker Series, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1428; 243301; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Conversations about America, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1429; 243302; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 13 Nov 2008; cuid1430; 243303; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - The Global Burden of a Chronic Disease: A Rising Epidemic, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1431; 243304; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Global Financial Crisis and Future Impact, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1432; 243305; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1433; 243306; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1434; 243307; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Institute of Ancient World: Speaker Mario Savio, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1435; 243308; 3 minidvs (Box 78)
  - APA Dumpling & Dynasty: Morning Panels, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1436; 243309; 11 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Parents Day, 18 Oct 2008; cuid1437; 243310; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1438; 243311; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1439; 243312; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - MTA Ravitch Hearings Session 1 & 2, 15 Sep 2008; cuid1440; 243313; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Martha Wilson Documentation: Dilemmas, undated; cuid1441; 243315; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Fales Food Series, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1442; 243316; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Sword of Judith Conference, 18 Apr 2008; cuid1443; 243314; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - SARI Economics Interview, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1444; 243317; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Stern CFR Panel #3, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1445; 243318; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - American Cheeses by Clark Wolf at Fales, 3 Dec 2008; cuid1446; 243319; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - How Food and Food Writing have Changed, 20 Nov 2008; cuid1447; 243320; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Hemmerding T. Haynes, 4 Dec 2008; cuid1448; 243321; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Filming Science (Secrecy), 19 Nov 2008; cuid1449; 243322; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Siemans Science Competition 2008, 7 Dec 2008; cuid1450; 243323; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - HR: HIPAA Training Videos at Benefits, 5 Dec 2008; cuid1451; 243325; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Global Public Health Event: Human Rights, 23 Jan 2009; cuid1452; 243326; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Economics DRI Conference, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1453; 243327; 4 videocassettes (dvcam)
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1454; 243328; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1455; 243329; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Donor Interviews: Tammiment Library, 11 Dec 2008; cuid1456; 243330; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - What Would the Poor Say: Debates in Aid, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1457; 243331; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Reynolds: Social Entrepreneurship Chuck D Series, 26 Jan 2009; cuid1458; 243332; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 20091; cuid1459; 243333; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 2009; cuid1460; 243334; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - MLK Marquee Event, 22 Jan 2009; cuid1461; 243335; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Court Reform in China, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1462; 243336; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Jim Abramson, 10 Feb 2009; cuid1463; 243337; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Zuckerman Forum 2009 Sessions 1,2,3, 13 Feb 2009; cuid1464; 243338; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - YNH Coming Up Slates, undated; cuid1465; 243339; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Program Office: Big fun Day, undated; cuid1466; 243340; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - University Wide Rooftop Shoot, undated; cuid1467; 243341; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Ahecha Move B-Roll, undated; cuid1468; 243342; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Exterior Campus Reel, 6 Jun 2002; cuid1469; 243343; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Staff Interview, 6 Jun 20021; cuid1470; 243344; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - John Sexton Martin Luther King Jr. Address, undated; cuid1471; 243345; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Recognizing and Responding to Students in Need, 23 Feb 2009; cuid1472; 243346; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1473; 243347; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1474; 243348; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1475; 243349; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1476; 243350; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Stern: Sani Lecture, 9 Mar 2009; cuid1477; 243351; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - SHARP: Lecture Series: United States, 24 Nov 2008; cuid1478; 243352; 2 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge: Inernational Relations, 4 Mar 2009; cuid1479; 243353; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Restored Financial Stability, 6 Mar 2009; cuid1480; 243354; 11 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - UVL 2009, 26 Feb 2009; cuid1481; 243355; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1482; 243356; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NCDP Session 3: Afternoon Sessions, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1483; 243357; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - New Multilateralism: Gordon M. Brown, 25 Mar 2009; cuid1484; 243358; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Fales: Food and Celebration: A Long History, 5 Mar 2009; cuid1485; 243359; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Tamiment Conference: Academic Freedom, 3 Apr 2009; cuid1486; 243360; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Michael Bllomberg and Non-Profits, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1487; 243361; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYU Alumni and Friends, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1488; 243362; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Courant: Jack Schwartz Memorial, 26 Mar 2009; cuid1489; 243363; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1490; 243364; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - GPH: Health in Africa, 16 Apr 2009; cuid1491; 243365; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Courant Spring Lecture, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1492; 243366; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1493; 243367; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1494; 243368; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - The 2009 Zuckerman Forum, 21 Apr 2009; cuid1495; 243369; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - Fales Library: Annual Fales Lecture, 14 Apr 2009; cuid1496; 243370; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Media Talk with David Carr and Tina Brown, 25 Feb 2009; cuid1497; 243371; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Scholars and Artists: George Stoney, 29 Apri 2009; cuid1498; 243372; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Aramark: Opera Performance, 26 Apr 2009; cuid1499; 243373; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Reynolds Social Entrepreneurial, 30 Apr 2009; cuid1500; 243374; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Obama's 100 Days, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1501; 243375; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - National Public Policy Forum, 18 Apr 2009; cuid1502; 243376; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Progress Review and Report, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1503; 243377; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Shared Care Integrated, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1504; 243378; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Depression Identification, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1505; 243379; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Period 3 and Beyond, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1506; 243380; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting: A Shared Vision for a Sustainable Region, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1507; 243381; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Ninth Annual Cal Ramsey, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1508; 243382; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - CAS: From Slavery to Freedom, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1509; 243383; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Scholars and Artists, 30 Sep 2008; cuid1510; 243384; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Coles Science Salon, 1 Oct 2008; cuid1511; 243385; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1512; 243386; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - CAS From Slavery to Freedom, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1513; 243387; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - What's Next? The Global Financial Crisis, 20 Oct 2008; cuid1514; 243388; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Arthur Miller, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1515; 243389; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Crossing the Line, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1516; 243390; 2 minidvs (Box 80)
  - Emerging and Disappering Immigrant, 16 Oct 2008; cuid1517; 243391; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Global Public Health: Rethinking HIV, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1518; 243392; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - President of Albania, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1519; 243393; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Conscious Capitalism, 8 Oct 2008; cuid1520; 243394; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - New Israel Fund, undated; cuid1521; 243395; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Rudin CTR: Making the Connection, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1522; 243396; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Moving the Needle: Improving Collaboration, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1523; 243397; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Depression Treatment, 25 Oct 2009; cuid1524; 243398; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Stern CFR Panel #1, 11 Nov 2008; cuid1525; 243399; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - King David Gala, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1526; 243400; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Podcast: The Emergency Economic, 29 Oct 2008; cuid1527; 243401; 0 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership Powerpoint, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1528; 243402; 0 electronic discs (cd-rom) (Box 80)
  - Rudin Conference "Closing the Gap", 4 Jun 2014; cuid1529; 243403; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - NCRW National Council for Research on Women, 6 Jun 2006; cuid1530; 243404; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Steinhardt Reading Recovery, 4 Jun 2008; cuid1531; 243405; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - SMPTE-NY Meeting "File Exchange", 4 Jun 2008; cuid1532; 243406; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National Presidential Caucus: 2012 Primary, 24 Jun 2008; cuid1533; 243407; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1534; 243408; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1535; 243409; 16 minidvs (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1536; 243436; 20 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute, 9 Jul 2008; cuid1537; 243410; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute Day Two, 10 Jul 2008; cuid1538; 243411; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Keynote, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1539; 243412; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 1 "Rewriting the Bible", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1540; 243413; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 2 "The Dead Sea Sect", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1541; 243414; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 3 "The Scrolls and Second Temple Judaism", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1542; 243415; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 4 "Judean Desert Texts", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1543; 243416; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Public Affairs Spotlight Shoot: Raw Footage, Penny Halkitis, Ann Morning, and Rough Cut, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1544; 243417; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 81)
  - Neil Postman: Raw Footage and Select Segments, undated; cuid1545; 243418; 3 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: LGBT Issues, undated; cuid1546; 243419; 4 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Washington Square News, undated; cuid1547; 243420; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: WNYU, undated; cuid1548; 243421; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Career Services, undated; cuid1549; 243422; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1550; 243423; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS 1: American Idioms Seminar, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1551; 243424; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS 2: Mixed Drinks American, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1552; 243425; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Interview with University Archivist Nancy Cricco, undated; cuid1553; 243426; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Clinton on Campus: Registration Campaign, 24 Apr 2002; cuid1554; 243427; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Conversations with Jie Tao, 15 Oct 1997; cuid1555; 243428; 1 sound cassettes (dat) (Box 81)
  - New York University in London, 28 Nov 2001; cuid1556; 243429; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Fall 2002, 1 Oct 2002; cuid1557; 243430; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Dogeaters: From Novel to the Stage, 30 Jan 2001; cuid1558; 243431; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: Skirball, 21 Aug 2008; cuid1559; 243432; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1560; 243433; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1561; 243437; 8 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sept 2008; cuid1562; 243434; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Simon Peres, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1563; 243435; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Martha Graham Panels, 18 Sep 2008; cuid1564; 243438; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Fales A.I.R. Gallery, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1565; 243439; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Financial Access Initiative: Program Feed, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1566; 243440; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Wagner Financial Access Initiative Event, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1567; 243441; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - A Discussion with UK Foreign Secretary, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1568; 243442; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Key Learning and Summary of Day 1, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1569; 243443; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Strategies for Sustaining, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1570; 243444; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Self Managment Team, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1571; 243445; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Progress Review, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1572; 243446; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Depression Care Workflow, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1573; 243447; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Primary Care Benefit, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1574; 243448; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Understanding the Importance, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1575; 243449; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Advanced Self Management, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1576; 243450; 1 minidvs (Box 81)